Guide to the Historic Photograph Subject File circa 19th century-20th century
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 5: Cities and Towns
  - Seattle - ocean liner, fishing boats and aerial view of Seattle Yacht Club, 3 items (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Seattle - Boat Season, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 6.1)
  - Seattle - Lake Union wintering grounds/dry dock, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Seattle - "Mosquito Fleet" fishing fleet, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Seattle - Skyline view from water, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Seattle - Pioneer Square, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Seattle - water front, Port of Seattle, Fleet Week, 19 items (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Seattle - "Shanty Town" water front dwellings, 4 items (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Seattle - harbor views - Coleman Ferry Term., 8 items (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Seattle - unloading cement - Duwamish waterway, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Seattle - George Washington Memorial bridge and others, 11 item (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Seattle - Smith's Cove - port terminal, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Seattle - O'Dea Catholic H.S., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Seattle - St. Theresa's Shrine of the Little Flower, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Seattle - Church of our Lady - Queen of Martyrs 1924, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Seattle - St. Mark's Cathedral, 1937, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Seattle - Trinity Parish Church, 1937, 4 items (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Seattle - Plymouth Church, 1906, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Seattle - St. James Cathedral, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Seattle - Statue of Christ, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Seattle - St. Edwards Seminary, 1935, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Seattle - St. Patrick's church and school, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Seattle - St. Paul's orphanage, 1932, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Seattle - First Church of Christ, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Seattle - Arboretum, 1937, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Seattle - Magnolia Bluff, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Seattle - Green Lake Recreation, 4 items (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Seattle - Woodland Park Zoo, 5 items (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Seattle - Kinnear and Jefferson Parks, 3 items (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Seattle - Seward Park, 5 items (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Seattle - Frye Art Museum, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Seattle - Music and Art Foundation, 3 items (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Seattle - Sudakoff Russian Art Center, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Seattle - Frozen Fish Museum, 3 items (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Seattle - W. Seattle Recreation Area and Laurelhurst field house, Sept. 23, 1935, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Seattle - Denny Home, June 7, 1937, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Seattle - Stacy House and Samuel Hill House, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Seattle - Art Museum, 14 items (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Seattle - Seattle Opera House, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 42.1)
  - Seattle - Alki Point, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Seattle - Broadmoor residential district, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Seattle - Lakes Union and Washington houseboats, 7 items (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Seattle - Ferry on Lake Washington, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Seattle - Hwys - Lake Washington Blvd, Alaskan Hwy, and Aurora Ave, 5 items (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Seattle Air Terminal and Boeing Co. field, 3 items (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Seattle - Pac. Coast Condensed Milk Factory, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Seattle - Cedar Lumber MFG Co., 1 item (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Seattle - Longacres Racetrack, 1933, 1935, 1936, 9 items (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Seattle - Seafair Parade, 1939, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Seattle - Potlatch Summer Festival, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Seattle - Japanese Harvest Festival (Bon Odori), 3 items (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Seattle - W.P.A. - theatre project - scene from "Stevedore", 1 item (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Seattle - Tilikum Place - Chief Seattle Monument, June 7, 1937, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Seattle - Volunteer Park, 9 items (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Seattle - Totem Pole - Northgate Shopping Center, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 57.1)
  - "Birth of Seattle" Monument, Alki Point, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - "Battle of Seattle" Monument, May, 1937, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Seattle - Corporate Seal, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Seattle - Building Steel Structures, 2 items (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Seattle-Tacoma International Airport - Lobby, 1 item (Box 11, Folder 61.1)
  - Seaside, Oregon, 3 items (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Shaniko, OR, 5 items (Box 11, Folder 62.1)
  - Shumway - Junior High School, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Shelton - panorama and post office mural, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Silverton, OR - Silver Creek Canyon Falls Album, 12 items (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Spaulding, ID - Sacajawea Museum, 1966, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Spokane - city panoramas, 10 items (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Spokane - Ft. George Wright, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Spokane - Northern Pacific Train Depot, 9/1883, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Spokane - buildings - Hazen and Jaeger Funeral Home, Masonic Temple, Grace Campbell Memorial Bldg., Federal Building, Old Federal Land Bank, Civic Center, Washington Water Power, etc., 23 items (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Spokane Falls Dam and Monroe Street bridge, 15 items (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Spokane Falls - birds eye view, 1884, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Spokane - House built in 1810, 4 items (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Spokane - Cemeteries, 3 items (Box 12, Folder 11.1)
  - Spokane - City Water Project, 1925-1926, 3 items (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Spokane - churches, 6 items (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Spokane - Gonzaga University, 4 items (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Spokane - Whitworth and Spokane Junior Colleges, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Spokane - Old Log Cabin, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Spokane - early panoramas, 5 items (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Spokane - hotels, 10 items (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Spokane - residential districts, 4 items (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Spokane - Felts Field - 41st Division Hdqr., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Spokane - early panoramas, 5 items (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Spokane - High Schools, 8 items (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Spokane - City Hall and County Courthouse, 4 items (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Spokane River, 7 items (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Spokane - Public Library, 1939, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Spokane - Municipal Airport, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Spokane - parks, 22 items (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Spokane - Epnorth League, 1897, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Spokane - Carstens Packing Co., 1 item (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Spokane - parade - pioneer impersonators, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Spokane - exposition advertisements, 1915, 4 items (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Spokane - recreation, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Spokane - postcards, 11 items (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Steilacoom - Western State Hospital, Old Church, Deep Sea Aquarium, old jail, 5 items (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Steptoe High School, 1909, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Funeral near Steptoe Butte, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Stevens Co. - school house, c. 1895, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Summerland, B.C. - August 18, 1920, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Sumner - public library, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Sunnyside - catholic church, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Tacoma - Fort Nisqually, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Tacoma - plat maps, 1873, 4 items (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Tacoma - early panoramas from 1875-1884, 3 items (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Tacoma - panorama 1885, 3 items (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Tacoma - early panoramas, 6 items (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Tacoma - parks, 9 items (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Tacoma - harbor views, 3 items (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Tacoma - Pierce Co. Courthouse and business dist., 2 items (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Tacoma - First Post Office, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Tacoma - smelter, 3 items (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Tacoma - buildings, 11 item (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Tacoma - Totem Pole and Wooden Indian, 1937, 3 items (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Tacoma - Public Schools, 7 items (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Tacoma - churches, 6 items (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Tacoma - Sutters Rockery, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Tacoma - Golf and Country Club, 2 items (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Tacoma - airports, 4 items (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Tacoma - Sodium Vapor Lamps on US99, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Tacoma - Washington State Museum - Isaac Stevens Collection, 5 items (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Tacoma - "Old Town" early 1890's, 1 item (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Tekoa, 16 items (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Tokeland - oyster beds, 1914, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Toppenish - Winthrop's cabin and church, 2 items (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Troy, ID, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Umatilla, OR - hotel, Feb. 20, 1937, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Union, OR - hotel, c.1920, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Union Flat - Feb. 1909, 4 items (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Uniontown - July 4, 1887 parade, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Uniontown - c.1910, 36 items (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Uniontown - panoramas, 3 items (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Uniontown - buildings, 7 items (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Valley - farmland meadows, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Vancouver - Army buildings, 4 items (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Vancouver - oldest apple tree in the northwest, 2 items (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Vancouver - buildings, 7 items (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Vancouver, B.C. - Burrard Inlet and Vancouver Harbor, 2 items (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - English Bay, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 16.1)
  - Rock Gardens, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 16.2)
  - Victoria, B.C. - panorama, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Butchart Gardens, Victoria, Canada, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 17.1)
  - Empress Hotel, Victoria, BC, 6 items (Box 13, Folder 17.2)
  - Waitsburg - Waitsburg band, 1908, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Walla Walla - town album, 1905-1910, 27 items (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Walla Walla - parade, pre-1900, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Walla Walla - 1st immigrant train, 1842, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Walla Walla - sketch, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Walla Walla - Board of County Commissioners 1901 - 1902, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Walla Walla - Steptoe Survivors, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Walla Walla - postcards, 1847-1940, 9 items (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Walla Walla - historical figures, 3 items (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Walla Walla - Pioneer Park, N.P. Depot, church, Veteran's Hospital, Union Bulletin, penitentiary, 15 items (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Walla Walla - Whitman College, 4 items (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Walla Walla - aerial view, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Walla Walla - canning company, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Walla Walla - 1930's flood, 6 items (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Walla Walla - Washington State Prison, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Wallace, ID -, 2 items (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Wallula Junction - c. 1900, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Washington D.C. - memorials, 12 items (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Waterville - railroad yards, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Waverly - Dashiel cabin, 7 items (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Wawawai - early 1900's, 10 items (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Wenatchee - buildings, 6 items (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Wenatchee Valley, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Westport - U.S. Naval Radio Station and salmon trolling fleet, 2 items (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Whitebird, ID - c.1908, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - White Salmon - Main Street, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Wilkson - schoolroom, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Winchester, ID - September, 1910, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Winona, 1 item (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Winthrop, WA, 5 items (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Yakima - street scenes various dates, inc. 5 sewage treatment photos, 8 items (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Yakima - churches, 2 items (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Yakima - buildings, 10 items (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Series 6: University of Washington
  - Administration Building, 5 items (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 1.1)
  - Suzzallo library, 6 items (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Education Hall, Forestry Bldg., Commerce and Philosophy Hall, Home Ec. bldg., 3 items (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Old Stone Observatory, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Washington State Museum and Japanese room, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Floating Theatre "The Showboat", 3 items (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - The Columns Memorial, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - The Chimes Tower, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Oceanographic bldgs, San Juan Island, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Rowing Crew and Coach Al Lilbrickson, 3 items (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Stadium and Athletic Pavilion, 4 items (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Campus map, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Aerial Photographs, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 12.1)
- Series 7: Expositions
  - Whitman's Bible and Elizabeth M. Sager's book 1847, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Yukon Pacific Expo., Seattle, 1909, 34 items (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - World's Fair, Chicago - Washington exhibit, 1933, 3 items (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - San Francisco's Golden Gate Expo., 1939-1940, 8 items (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - World's Fair - New York, 1939-1940, 14 items (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - American Expo. - New Orleans, 1885-1886, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Fort Clatsop, Oregon, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 18.1)
- Series 8: Forts and Blockhouses
  - Fort Colville - sketches from mid-1800's, 6 items (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Fort Lewis, 22 items (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Fort Logan, MT, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Fort Missoula MT, 3 items (Box 14, Folder 21.1)
  - Fort Nisqually, 8 items (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Fort Okanogan, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Fort Rains Blockhouse, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Fort Sherman, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Fort Simcoe, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Old Fort Spokane, c.1925, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Fort Steilacoom - General's residence, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Fort Vancouver - 1936-1937, 5 items (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Fort Walla Walla -, 10 items (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Fort Wright, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Felt's Field, 17 items (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Alexander Blockhouse, Coupeville, Whidbey Island, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Borst Blockhouse, Centralia, WA, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Crockett Blockhouse, Whidbey Is., c.1938, 12 items (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Davis Blockhouse, Coupeville, Whidbey Is., 7 items (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Jacob Ebey Blockhouse, Whidbey Is., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - English Blockhouse, Garrison Bay - San Juan Is., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - British Camp Monument, Garrison Bay, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Marcus Blockhouse, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Blockhouse and railroad, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Unidentified blockhouses, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Series 9: Hunting and Fishing
  - Misc. catches: salmon, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Fish Catch, Grays Harbor, Washington, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 43.1)
  - Snake River sturgeon, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - North Dakota hunting, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Purse seining on Puget Sound, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Fisherman at camp - Grays Harbor, c.1900, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Loomis Lake bass fishing, Sept., 1931, 2 items (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Mountain Lake fishing, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Razor Clams, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Fur pelts, 3 items (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Gov. Frank Hunt (ID) and escort party, c.1903, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Hunting scenes - goat, deer, elk, 3 items (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Hunting deer in Okanagan region, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Series 10: Industry
  - Small portable mill, 1905, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Old waffle iron, 1959, 4 items (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Fisher Flour Mills, Seattle, 1930's, 3 items (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Crescent Manufacturing Co., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Grist Mill - Fort Colville, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Puyallup Fruit Cannery, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Weyerhauser, Rayonier, and wood pulp plants, 3 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Everett Pulp and Paper Co., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Lake Washington canal lumber mill, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Unloading fishing barge - Aberdeen, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - San Juan Fish Company - Seattle, 8 items (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Royal Chinook salmon, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Fish in cold storage, Port of Seattle, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Canned salmon, 3 items (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Salmon cannery - Bellingham, WA, 2 items (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Wheel traps - Columbia River, 2 items (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Brailing a salmon trap, 2 items (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - First salmon hatchery - Chinook, WA, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Oyster Industry, 5 items (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Northport smelting and refining Co., 1904, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Superior Portland Cement Inc. - Concrete, WA, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Lake Union drydock and machine works plant, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Pacific Car and Foundry plant - Renton, WA, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Building 8-oared racing shells, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Series 11: Indians
  - Portraits by Eve Rockwell Little- Chief Joseph, Chief Looking Glass, 3 items (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Portraits of Chief Joseph c. 1877-c. 1904, 12 items (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Chief Joseph at Nespelem, 1903, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Chief Joseph's sister and niece, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Chief Looking Glass, 3 items (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Peo Peo Tholekt, 1916 (Yellow Bull), 3 items (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Long Haired Alec, 2 items (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Whitebird, Nez Perce chief, July 12, 1879, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Native American Portraits, 6 items (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Harrison Lott, Lapwai ID, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Jackson Sundown 1863-1923, 2 items (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Mattie Howeattle - Quillayute Indian, 1959, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Chief Isaac-Kootenai, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Jones Frank-Spalding ID, 1936, 7 items (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Chief Kamiaken, 1864, 2 items (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Chief Joe Kentuck- Nez Perce, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Kills Two-an Indian Warrior, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Native American in traditional dress Nez Perce, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Albert Moore-Nez Perce, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Eustace Markistum-Makah, 1936, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Makah woman, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 20.1)
  - Ellen Moses, c. 1936, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "Grandma" Moses-Nez Perce Matriarch, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Mourning Dove, 1916, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Princess Pretty Cloud, 1936, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Chief Red Cloud, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Josiah Red Wolf, Nez Perce, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Sacajawea Statue, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Lizzie Scott, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Chief Seattle (drawing), 1 item (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Spokane Garry, 9 items (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Spotted Tail, Brule Sioux chief, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Chief Te-te-ho-not, 3 items (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Timothy- Nez Perce chief (reprint), 1 item (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Chief Sam Tilden- Nez Perce, 5 items (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Chief Tommy Thompson, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Three Feathers, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Two Moon- Nez Perce, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Rev. Harry Wheeler- Nez Perce, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Jonas Whitebear, 2 items (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Yellow Wolf (drawing), 1 item (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Reprints of photos taken by William Jefferson Carpenter: portrait, Native Americans, 7 items (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Mary- Chief Moses' wife, and residence, 4 items (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Sitting Bull, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Ben Wolf- great-great-grandson of Lone Wolf, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Ellen Moses- 1936, 2 items (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Amy Tilden- great-grandniece of Chief Joseph, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Unidentified Native Americans, 12 items (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Smelt Fishing, Washington, 1 item (Box 16, Folder 47.1)
  - Unidentified Native American women, 8 items (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Children by tepees, 3 items (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Native American children, 8 items (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Washington State Fair, 1909, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Photo of Charles Russell water color: travois, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Burial sites: Old Ft. Colville and Walla Walla road, 1914; along Snake River near Bishop c. 1903, 2 items (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Princess Angelina, 1895 (Chief Seattle's daughter), 2 items (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Gathering of 14 chiefs, some unknown, from Spokane, Kalispell, and Flathead tribes, 2 items (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Eight leaders, US Captain and nephew of US Senator, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Various Indian camps: Blue Mts., Potlatch, Wawawai, Lewiston, 5 items (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Indian Valley, ID; Big Hole Battlefield, MT; Camas Prairie, 4 items (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Chief Black Eagle and Ida Black Eagle, 2 items (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Bust of Chief Joseph, 2 items (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Salmon bake, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Peo Peo Tah Likt's burial site, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Chief Joseph sites: birthplace, burial site, 4 items (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Induction of Dean Monroe into Nez Perce tribe, 1936, 2 items (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Celebration at Omak c. 1925, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Old Native American scenes, 8 items (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Nootka Village, 1778, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Tlingit family at Funter Bay, Alaska, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Quillayute Indians: canoes, 3 items (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Makah: basket weavers, fishermen, hunters, etc., 7 items (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Makah: woodcarvers, 4 items (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Lummi tribesmen, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Muckleshoot, 1909, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Supplies headed for Crow Creek Res. and Warm Springs Agency, OR, 9 items (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Rev. Reuben speech / Rev. Reuben pupils, 6 items (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Nez Perce at Spaulding Museum c. 1934, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Nez Perce at Lapwai, 3 items (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Nez Perce at Spaulding, 5 items (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Nez Perce: family, dance, pictograph (1905), 3 items (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Nez Perce, 3 items (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Nez Perce: Peo Peo Talek, Halla Ne Tsa, Charlie Willpakim, et al, 8 items (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Kootenai Conference, 5/31/11- Bonners Ferry ID, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Nez Perce- photo album and portraits: Elijah Williams, Young Felix, Mose George, et al; Jackson Sundown, etc., 9 items (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Umatilla Reservation and Boarding School (1891), 5 items (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Camps near Spokane, 2 items (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Non-treaty Indians c. 1877-80 (Nez Perce) [93-141], 2 items (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Ceremonial Induction into Blackfoot tribe, Glacier National Park, 1928, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Chemawa Indian School near Salem, OR, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Yakima Indians, 8 items (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Wanapum Indians, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Sweat bath; spruce frame, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - School at Lapwai, 1922, 1 item (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Churches: Lapwai, White Swan, and Stevens Co., 4 items (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - DeSmet, ID, mission and homes c. 1935, 7 items (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Shoshone/Bannock snapshots, 10 items (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Grass mat long houses, 2 items (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Teepees, 6 items (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Canoes, 4 items (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Baskets and Cornhusk bags, 5 items (Box 18, Folder 6)